schoolforstartups.co.uk 2015-11-25

# Privacy Policy | School for Startups

This privacy policy governs the privacy of the visitors who choose to use this website.

The policy outlines the obligations & requirements of the users and website owners, and sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned. The way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information is also detailed within this policy.

## The Website

This website and it’s owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.

## Contact and Communication

Users contacting this website and/or it’s owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998\. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.

This website and it’s owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.

## Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. You can read our cookie policy [here](http://www.schoolforstartups.co.uk/cookie-policy/)

Cookies are small files saved to the users computers hard drive that track, save and store  
information about the users interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through it’s server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and it’s external serving vendors.

This website uses tracking software to monitor it’s visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The  
software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your  
engagement and usage of the website but will not store, save or collect personal information. For further information you can read Google’s privacy policy here: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>.

Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.

## Social Media Platforms

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and it’s owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor it’s owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

## Resources and Further Information

  * Data Protection Act 1998
  * Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003
  * Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 – The Guide
  * Twitter Privacy Policy
  * Facebook Privacy Policy
  * Google Privacy Policy
  * Linkedin Privacy Policy
  * Mailchimp Privacy Policy
